

Tarek BEN YAHIA

Future Software Engineer

Currently student in 5th and last year of my studies in software engineering cycle, I'm searching for an end-of-studies internship .I chose mobile development as a specialty and I really enjoy it . I have a good experience working with Flutter and Native Android ,acquired thanks to my academic projects and freelance experience .I also have some graphic design and web development skills that I developed during my first years at the university. I am a very curious person, I always want to learn new things and new technologies and work with them to develop my skills. I like working in a team, it allows me to learn new things among other things. I am also very dynamic, and good communicator.

+210

+216 24 760 280



Tarek.benyahia@esprit.tn



Tunis, Tunisia



Click to Visit Website



Click to visit my LinkedIn



Click to Visit my Github

SKILLS

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Critical thinking

TECHNOLOGIES

Flutter | Android | Node.JS | HTML | CSS | PHP | JAVA | SQL | JavaScript | MongoDB | Github | Docker | Symfony

LANGUAGES

- Arabic Maternal
- French Bilingual
- English B2
- German B2

Clubs and associative life

- 2017-2019 : AIESEC Member (Marketeer)
- 2018-2020 :Inceptum Junior Entreprise Member at sales pole

EDUCATION

- ESPRIT(Private High School of Engineering and Technologies) | 2016 Today
 - software engineering degree
- Pioneer School of Ariana | 2012 2016
 - Tunisian Baccalaureate (Experimental Sciences)

EXPERIENCE

- Freelancer | 2017 To Today
 - Mobile development (Android , Flutter, Node. JS (Backend))
 - Web development (Symfony)
 - Graphic Design (Photoshop, Illustrator, After effects, Premiere Pro)
- Arduino Trainer | 2017 To Dec 2018
 - Association Jeunes Science de Tunisie (AJST), Tunisia
 - Teached kids from 7 to 18 basics of Arduino programming
- Web Developer | 2018 To Dec 2020
 - Print Group, Tunisia
 - Web Development using Symfony
- Mobile Development Internship(Flutter) | 2019 2020
 - Scar Interactives, Tunisia
 - > Frontend application with Flutter
 - Backend Development using Node.JS
- Mobile Development Internship(Android) | July 2021 To Sept 2021
 - Yes-SERV Architecture, Tunisia
 - > Frontend application with Android
 - Backend Development using Node.JS

ACADEMIC PROJECTS (Group projects)

- 2D Video Game | 2016-2017
 - Developed using SDL (C Language)
- * CRM Platform | Sept. 2017 To Jan. 2018
 - Developed with QT (C++)
- E-Commerce Website | Jan. 2018 To June 2018
 - Developed with Native php
- Hunting management platform | Sept.2019 May 2020
 - > 3 Platforms: Web (Symfony), Desktop (JavaFX), Mobile (Android)
- **Barter Mobile Application** | Sept. 2020 To Dec. 2020
 - Developed with Native Android and Node.JS
- Cross-Platform Application for Lawyers | Jan. 2020 To June 2020
 - > Developed with Flutter (mobile) ,Angular (Web) and Node.JS + Docker

CERTIFICATIONS

- Introduction to HTML5(University of Michigan)(Coursera)
- Introduction Psychology (YALE University)(Coursera)
- Fundamentals of Graphic Design (Califonia Institute of the Arts)(Coursera)
- Java For Android (Vanderbilt University)(Coursera)
- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (Google Digital Garage)
- Multiplatform Mobile App Development with React Native (The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology)(Coursera)
- The French language test (TCF)